<slides>
	<slide>
		<title>First slide</title>
		<subtitle>
			Subtitle 1
		</subtitle>
		<content>
			<ul>
				<li>
					I don't know what you could say about a day in which you have seen
					four beautiful sunsets.
				</li>
				<li>
					For those who have seen the Earth from space, and for the hundreds
					and perhaps thousands more who will, the experience most certainly changes
					your perspective. The things that we share in our world are far more valuable
					than those which divide us.
				</li>
				<li>
					We choose to go to the moon in this decade and do the other things,
					not because they are easy, but because they are hard, because that goal will
					serve to organize and measure the best of our energies and skills, because
					that challenge is one that we are willing to accept, one we are unwilling to
					postpone, and one which we intend to win.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</content>
		<notes>
			<ul>
				<li>
					Spaceflights cannot be stopped. This is not the work of any one man
					or even a group of men. It is a historical process which mankind is carrying
					out in accordance with the natural laws of human development.
				</li>
				<li>
					We are all connected; To each other, biologically. To the earth,
					chemically. To the rest of the universe atomically.
				</li>
				<li>
					That's one small step for [a] man, one giant leap for mankind.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</notes>
	</slide>

	<slide>
		<title>Second slide</title>
		<subtitle>
			Subtitle 2
		</subtitle>
		<content>
			<ul>
				<li>
					Science has not yet mastered prophecy. We predict too much for the
					next year and yet far too little for the next 10.
				</li>
				<li>
					I don't know what you could say about a day in which you have seen
					four beautiful sunsets.
				</li>
				<li>
					There can be no thought of finishing for ‘aiming for the stars.’ Both
					figuratively and literally, it is a task to occupy the generations. And no
					matter how much progress one makes, there is always the thrill of just
					beginning.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</content>
		<notes>
			<ul>
				<li>
					As we got further and further away, it [the Earth] diminished in
					size. Finally it shrank to the size of a marble, the most beautiful you can
					imagine. That beautiful, warm, living object looked so fragile, so delicate,
					that if you touched it with a finger it would crumble and fall apart. Seeing
					this has to change a man.
				</li>
				<li>
					Failure is not an option.
				</li>
				<li>
					Here men from the planet Earth first set foot upon the Moon. July
					1969 AD. We came in peace for all mankind.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</notes>
	</slide>

	<slide>
		<title>Third slide</title>
		<subtitle>
			Subtitle 3
		</subtitle>
		<content>
			<ul>
				<li>
					Curious that we spend more time congratulating people who have
					succeeded than encouraging people who have not.
				</li>
				<li>
					As we got further and further away, it [the Earth] diminished in
					size. Finally it shrank to the size of a marble, the most beautiful you can
					imagine. That beautiful, warm, living object looked so fragile, so delicate,
					that if you touched it with a finger it would crumble and fall apart. Seeing
					this has to change a man.
				</li>
				<li>
					Across the sea of space, the stars are other suns.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</content>
		<notes>
			<ul>
				<li>
					As we got further and further away, it [the Earth] diminished in
					size. Finally it shrank to the size of a marble, the most beautiful you can
					imagine. That beautiful, warm, living object looked so fragile, so delicate,
					that if you touched it with a finger it would crumble and fall apart. Seeing
					this has to change a man.
				</li>
				<li>
					We have an infinite amount to learn both from nature and from each
					other
				</li>
				<li>
					You know, being a test pilot isn't always the healthiest business in
					the world.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</notes>
	</slide>

	<slide>
		<title>Fourth slide</title>
		<subtitle>
			Subtitle 4
		</subtitle>
		<content>
			<ul>
				<li>
					I believe every human has a finite number of heartbeats. I don't
					intend to waste any of mine
				</li>
				<li>
					We have an infinite amount to learn both from nature and from each
					other
				</li>
				<li>
					Astronomy compels the soul to look upward, and leads us from this
					world to another.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</content>
		<notes>
			<ul>
				<li>
					The dreams of yesterday are the hopes of today and the reality of
					tomorrow.
				</li>
				<li>
					The sky is the limit only for those who aren't afraid to fly!
				</li>
				<li>
					It suddenly struck me that that tiny pea, pretty and blue, was the
					Earth. I put up my thumb and shut one eye, and my thumb blotted out the
					planet Earth. I didn't feel like a giant. I felt very, very small.
				</li>
			</ul>
		</notes>
	</slide>
</slides>